pngarts.com 2019-07-20

# Privacy Policy | PNG Arts

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which pngarts.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the pngarts.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by pngarts.com.

##  Personal Identification Information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

##  Non-personal Identification Information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

##  Web Browser Cookies

This Website uses cookies. A cookie is a small, removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies allow you to place an order on this Website and allow us to enhance, facilitate and personalize your online surfing and shopping experience. For example, we use cookies to:

Recognize you when you return to this Website;  
Remember your stored preferences on this Website;  
Present relevant content to you when you visit this Website;  
Analyze visitor behavior; and  
Facilitate other similar type of activities.  
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your web browser settings.

If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your visit to this Website more efficient and enjoyable, and in some cases, some of our services will not function or will function with limited capability.

##  How we use collected information

pngarts.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  
– To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
– To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
– To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
– To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

##  How we Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.  
Sharing your Personal Information  
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

##  Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

##  Google AdSense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

##  Third Party Site Privacy Policy’s

**Google +1 Button –** <http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/plusone/>  
**Feedburner** – Newsletter at <http://www.feedburner.com/fb/a/privacy>  
**Facebook.com** – fan page, FaceBook like, share and send buttons; <http://www.facebook.com/policy.php>  
**Twitter.com** – Twitter tweet button; Twitter <http://twitter.com/privacy>  
**Pinterest.com** – Pinterest Pin button; Pinterest <http://pinterest.com/about/privacy/>

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

pngarts.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

##  Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

##  Contacting US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please [contact us](http://contact/) at: admin[@]pngarts.com
